solyndra.com 2010-10-08

# Solyndra - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Overview

Solyndra respects your concerns about privacy safeguards. This privacy policy discloses how we gather, use, share and protect information collected about visitors to the Solyndra Web site. Solyndra collects two different types of information: (1) email and/or other contact information you provide when contacting us; and (2) personally identifiable information collected as you visit and browse our Web site. By visiting the Solyndra Web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Solyndra encourages you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

### What Information Does Solyndra Gather?

Solyndra voluntarily collects information from visitors who express an interest in investing in a solar system. That data is shared with our dealers/installers who sell our systems so that they can contact these visitors. Solyndra may periodically conduct surveys, usability studies, contests and other programs that help Solyndra improve and promote its products and services. Visitors to our Web site may voluntarily participate in these programs and as a condition of such participation, they may be asked to provide additional demographic information. Solyndra may collect such additional information that visitors voluntarily provides, including, without limitation, gender, age, income level, modem speed, or type of operating system used. Personally identifiable information collected by Solyndra in conjunction with voluntary surveys, usability studies, contests and other voluntary programs will not be shared with any sponsor or third party without your consent.

### Visitor Information

The Solyndra Web site server automatically records visitor information based on your activity on the Solyndra Web site, such as visitor IP addresses and/or domain names. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the Internet such as your Internet service provider. This information is associated with you as an individual. Solyndra may use information about user behavior, user experience, user equipment, computing and internet environment to improve the performance of the Solyndra Web site.

### Communication Information

If you communicate directly with Solyndra by email, phone or letter, Solyndra may collect and store a record of your communication. Solyndra may use your communication information to respond to your issues and inquiries. Your communication information you provide to Solyndra's third party partners will also enable such partners to let us know that you have contacted them. Such communication information may be used to distribute information back to you about Solyndra, its products, or other promotional or information communications from Solyndra.

### Cookies

Cookies are data that a Web site transmits to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable the Web site to recognize your browser, record and store your information and occasionally track your viewing habits for statistical purposes. The Solyndra web site uses cookies to collect this type of information to deliver targeted content to you, and potentially tailor and enhance your experience on the Solyndra Web site.

### Children

Solyndra does not intend to collect information from individuals who identify themselves as under thirteen (13) years of age. If you are under thirteen, you should not provide any personal information on the Solyndra Web site. Solyndra will not knowingly disclose personally identifiable information of children under thirteen to any third party.

### How Does Solyndra Protect My Information?

Solyndra takes technical, contractual, administrative and physical security steps to protect all visitor and contact information from unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and enable the correct use of information. Solyndra utilizes security systems to protect such information.

### How Does Solyndra Use the Information and With Whom Do We Share the Information?

Solyndra does not share, rent, lease or sell personally identifiable information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Business Transfers Because the solar energy business is a rapidly evolving business, and Solyndra continues to develop and enhance its business, it may become subject to a corporate merger, corporate acquisition, or similar transaction involving the sale or combination of substantially all of its assets. In such circumstance, Solyndra reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information to the merged or resultant business entity.

### Protection of Solyndra and Others; Compliance with the Law

Solyndra reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with legal process, (b) respond to any claims against it, or (c) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Solyndra, its employees, its customers or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Linked Webs

The Solyndra Web site may contain links to other sites. Solyndra is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. Solyndra encourages you to review the privacy policies posted on these third party sites.

### Accessing and Updating Information

Please notify us of changes to any of your personally identifiable information that you have previously provided to us, including name, address, title, phone number or email address by sending an email to [legal@solyndra.com](mailto:legal@solyndra.com). To remove your name from our database or to interrupt e-mail notifications, please send an e-mail to [legal@solyndra.com](mailto:legal@solyndra.com).

### Conditions of Use; Contacting Us

Please check the Solyndra Web site frequently to see recent changes, additions and deletions to this Privacy Policy. If you prefer not to receive promotional or other informational communications from Solyndra, or if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or comments or suggestions about the Solyndra Web site, please send an email to [legal@solyndra.com](mailto:legal@solyndra.com) or by mail to Solyndra, Inc., 47700 Kato Road, Fremont, CA 94538, USA, Attention: Webmaster.
